

## Profile

Dedicated to great customer service and being a successful entrepreneur. Began thinking about successful marketing and business ideas at a young age when passing out flyer's to my neighbors offering to sell their unwanted items. I believe team work is very important and I want everyone around me to be successful. I was the senior team captain for the Layton High School golf team in 2019 and enjoy leading a team. I previously worked for Prime Communications working as a Retail Sales Manager, and I graduated from the University of Utah Full Stack Web Development boot camp in February 2020.

# **Employment History**

# Retail Sales Manager at Prime Communications, Sandy

August 2019 — December 2019

Started at the manager position in August 2019 working at the AT&T authorized retailer in Sandy, Utah. At this location I had one employee, but was eventually moved to Orem, Utah in October, here I had 4 employees. Manager duties consisted of making the schedule, daily management operations, meeting store wide sales goals, dealing with cash, and providing excellent customer service.

## Retail Sales Consultant at Prime Communications, Layton

March 2020 — July 2020

As Retail Sales Consultant, my job was to execute customer requests, up sell customers and meet my individual sales goals.

# Education

## Web Development, University of Utah, Sandy

August 2019 — February 2020

Attended a six month full stack web development program that is held by the University of Utah. The program is fueled by "Trilogy Education Services, a 2U, Inc".

## High School Diploma, Layton High, Layton

August 2016 — May 2019

## ■ References

**David Peterson from Prime Communications** 

801-244-0806

## Michael Bonner from University of Utah Bootcamp

michaelwbonner@gmail.com · 8018395287

# **Preston Hill from Prime Communications**

preston.r.hill@gmail.com · 801-441-9177

#### **Details**

South Jordan, 84009, 801-643-4908 cwchiz16@gmail.com

#### Links

My Portfolio

#### **Skills**

React Developer

**NoSQL Databases** 

Ability to Learn Quickly

Creative Problem Solving

Good team player

**Deadline Oriented** 

**SQL Databases** 

MongoDB

Express.js

JavaScript

node.js

gatsby.js

npm

HTML/CSS

#### **Hobbies**

Golf, Motocross, Football, Riding Motorcycles, Coding, Snowboarding, Motorcycle Mechanics